lyricsondemand.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Lyrics On Demand

Privacy Policy

**LyricsOnDemand.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and divulgence practices for this Web site: LyricsOnDemand.com 

**Third Party Advertising:**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

**Third Party Cookies:**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser. 

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via [privacy@exponential.com](mailto:privacy@exponential.com)

 **YouTube's API Client:**

This site uses the Youtube API to display related music videos on the song pages. No data or user information is being collected or stored related to the YouTube's API Client. Please reference [YouTube's Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/t/terms) for more information. More information on Google's privacy policy can be found [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy). Any further questions can be directed to [webmaster@lyricsondemand.com](mailto:webmaster@lyricsondemand.com)

 **Security:**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
